<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Education Growth Partners</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../../index.html</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 18:56:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Edmentum to Acquire Apex Learning, an Industry Leader in Virtual and Hybrid Learning for Middle and High School Students</title>
		<link>./../../../../edmentum-to-acquire-apex-learning-an-industry-leader-in-virtual-and-hybrid-learning-for-middle-and-high-school-students/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2430</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BLOOMINGTON, MN / ACCESSWIRE / June 22, 2021 / Edmentum (edmentum.com), a global pioneer in education technology, announced a definitive agreement to acquire Apex Learning, a Seattle-based industry leader in digital curriculum and virtual learning with over 20 years of deep expertise providing high-quality, rigorous, and teacher-centered programs. Apex&#8217;s mission of making a difference in [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-reader-unique-id="1"><strong data-reader-unique-id="2">BLOOMINGTON, MN / ACCESSWIRE / June 22, 2021 / </strong>Edmentum <a href="https://www.edmentum.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:(edmentum.com" data-rapid_p="7" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="3">(edmentum.com</a>), a global pioneer in education technology, announced a definitive agreement to acquire Apex Learning, a Seattle-based industry leader in digital curriculum and virtual learning with over 20 years of deep expertise providing high-quality, rigorous, and teacher-centered programs. Apex&#8217;s mission of making a difference in education complements Edmentum&#8217;s drive to amplify teaching and propel student learning forward. Together, these two organizations will support millions of students worldwide.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="4">&#8220;I am thrilled to welcome Apex into the Edmentum family,&#8221; said Jamie Candee, Edmentum CEO. &#8220;As the school year comes to an end and districts evolve into new models of teaching for the fall, so too must Edmentum continue to grow to meet those needs. Pairing Apex&#8217;s proven, high-quality secondary learning programs with Edmentum&#8217;s full suite of high-quality, online learning programs creates a rich array of offerings designed specifically for the next generation of learners. Together, in partnership with schools and districts globally, we will move education forward.&#8221;</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="5">Edmentum&#8217;s research-based approach offers hundreds of state- and nationally certified courses, supported by comprehensive consulting and educational services. Adding Apex&#8217;s credit-bearing core and elective courses, project-based technology courses, and student-targeted, standards-matching tutorials will create a new industry-leading model for virtual and hybrid learning programs.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="10">&#8220;I am incredibly proud of the positive impact that Apex&#8217;s programs and services have had with students and educators across the country,&#8221; said Chris Porter, Apex Learning CEO. &#8220;We are absolutely committed to high-quality learning content and scalable technology and are very tightly aligned to Edmentum&#8217;s strategic vision. As we come together to work with schools to help provide students flexible learning models, the possibilities are endless. I am thrilled for the next phase of Apex and our combined ability to accelerate world-class instructional solutions for all students and educators.&#8221;</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="11">Andy Kaplan, Managing General Partner at Education Growth Partners, Apex&#8217;s prior investor, said, &#8220;We look forward to seeing Apex and Edmentum further raise the bar for digital learning and better prepare students for success. We&#8217;re proud to see our belief and investment in Apex result in such an important event in the education technology market.&#8221;</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="12">The acquisition follows a strategic investment in Edmentum last year by Chicago-based private investment firm The Vistria Group that signaled new growth for Edmentum to address the learning needs of 21st-century classrooms.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="13">&#8220;This acquisition enriches Edmentum&#8217;s depth in middle and high school grades and strengthens the company&#8217;s commitment to delivering high-quality, research-based online learning to schools and districts across the globe,&#8221; said Phil Alphonse, Senior Partner at The Vistria Group. &#8220;Bringing these two organizations together will propel even more teachers and students forward and create countless opportunities for hybrid and virtual learning all over the world.&#8221;</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="14">Apex Learning customers and products will continue to be supported as Edmentum and Apex work in concert to provide the high-quality service and experience students and educators have come to expect.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="15">The international law firm of Winston &amp; Strawn LLP is acting as legal advisor to Edmentum. William Blair &amp; Company, LLC was the lead banker for Apex Learning. Alvarez &amp; Marsal and Cuesta Partners served in a consultant and advisory capacity as well. Kramer Levin Naftalis &amp; Frankel LLP is acting as legal advisor to Apex Learning.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="16"><strong data-reader-unique-id="17">About Edmentum</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="18">Edmentum, Inc., a global leader in education technology, is committed to helping educators individualize learning for every student through simple technology, high-quality content, and actionable data. Edmentum is committed to being educators&#8217; most trusted partner in creating successful student outcomes everywhere learning occurs. Built on 60 years of experience in education, Edmentum solutions like Edmentum Courseware, Exact Path, Study Island, and EdOptions Academy, currently support educators and students in more than 40,000 schools nationwide and internationally. For more information, visit <a href="http://link.email.dynect.net/link.php?DynEngagement=true&amp;H=tiMleQXvuhG3cVWUKKJFwgesMDniOk1PHbBHFzJ47RtQGrfqda%2FT%2FTRNHRe4oo%2BfkGgl6U5DPuq1YvywU6MvFqddoLvsptF3R5kMEbc9tGCYMJRyyRysVQ%3D%3D&amp;G=0&amp;R=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.edmentum.com%2F&amp;I=20161003125215.000001a9636c%40mail6-08-ewr&amp;X=MHwxMDQ2NzU4OjU3ZjI1NDc5MGU4NWI4NDA2M2RkNDQ1Mzs%3D&amp;S=jnFIz8VOBGb6WB_y-QYkJ_W8hfpyHR51G9ziJZh7fEw" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:edmentum.com" data-rapid_p="9" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="19">edmentum.com</a>.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="20"><strong data-reader-unique-id="21">About Apex Learning</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="22">An industry leader in digital learning with deep expertise in online learning, Apex Learning collaborates with school districts across the country to implement solutions proven to accelerate learning and create opportunities for student success in school and beyond. The company is driven by the understanding that supporting the needs of all students &#8211; from struggling to advanced &#8211; strengthens schools and creates stronger communities, brighter futures, and a more equitable world. Apex Learning is accredited by Cognia and its courses are approved for National Collegiate Athletic Association eligibility. Apex Learning, where opportunity thrives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.apexlearning.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:http://www.apexlearning.com/" data-rapid_p="10" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="23">http://www.apexlearning.com/</a>.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="24"><strong data-reader-unique-id="25">About Education Growth Partners</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="26">Education Growth Partners (&#8220;EGP&#8221;) is a private equity firm dedicated to investing in proven, high potential learning, knowledge, and workplace companies that offer compelling solutions to unmet needs. The extensive investment expertise of Education Growth Partners&#8217; team ensures its companies receive an infusion of highly strategic capital and insight that can accelerate their reach, scale, and impact to create long-term value. Our highly experienced team is composed of investors with operating experience who have a passion for education and behavior change and an understanding of the power of great companies to create opportunities for individuals, organizations, and systems. For more information, please visit <a href="http://www.edgrowth.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:www.edgrowth.com" data-rapid_p="11" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="27">www.edgrowth.com</a>.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="28"><strong data-reader-unique-id="29">About</strong><strong data-reader-unique-id="30">The Vistria Group</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="31">The Vistria Group is a Chicago-based private investment firm focused on investing in middle-market companies in the healthcare, education, and financial services sectors. Vistria&#8217;s team is comprised of highly experienced operating partners and private equity executives with proven track records of working with management teams in building innovative, market-leading companies. For more information, please visit <a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2684714-1&amp;h=1474294993&amp;u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vistria.com%2F&amp;a=www.vistria.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:www.vistria.com" data-rapid_p="12" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="32">www.vistria.com</a>.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="33"><strong data-reader-unique-id="34">Media Contacts</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="35"><strong data-reader-unique-id="36">Edmentum:</strong><br data-reader-unique-id="37" />Ashlee Tatum-Eckley<br data-reader-unique-id="38" /><a href="mailto:ashlee.tatum-eckley@edmentum.com" data-ylk="slk:ashlee.tatum-eckley@edmentum.com" data-rapid_p="13" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="39">ashlee.tatum-eckley@edmentum.com</a><br data-reader-unique-id="40" />214.294.9904</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="41"><strong data-reader-unique-id="42">The Vistria Group:</strong><br data-reader-unique-id="43" />Kevin Sajdak<br data-reader-unique-id="44" />Res Publica Group<br data-reader-unique-id="45" /><a href="mailto:ks@respublicagroup.com" data-ylk="slk:ks@respublicagroup.com" data-rapid_p="14" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="46">ks@respublicagroup.com</a><br data-reader-unique-id="47" />312.755.3547</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="48"><strong data-reader-unique-id="49">SOURCE:</strong> Edmentum</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="50"><br data-reader-unique-id="52" />View source version on accesswire.com: <br data-reader-unique-id="53" /><a href="https://www.accesswire.com/652677/Edmentum-to-Acquire-Apex-Learning-an-Industry-Leader-in-Virtual-and-Hybrid-Learning-for-Middle-and-High-School-Students" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:https://www.accesswire.com/652677/Edmentum-to-Acquire-Apex-Learning-an-Industry-Leader-in-Virtual-and-Hybrid-Learning-for-Middle-and-High-School-Students" data-rapid_p="15" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="54">https://www.accesswire.com/652677/Edmentum-to-Acquire-Apex-Learning-an-Industry-Leader-in-Virtual-and-Hybrid-Learning-for-Middle-and-High-School-Students</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Workplace Culture &#038; Compliance Platform Emtrain Hires Software Leader and Inclusion Activist Odessa Jenkins as the Company’s First President</title>
		<link>./../../../../workplace-culture-compliance-platform-emtrain-hires-software-leader-and-inclusion-activist-odessa-jenkins-as-the-companys-first-president/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 16:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2426</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO (April 14, 2021) &#8212; Emtrain, which delivers workplace culture analytics through its online training platform to prevent bias, discrimination, harassment and ethical lapses in the workplace, today announced it has hired Odessa (OJ) Jenkins to be the company’s first president. Emtrain’s founder Janine Yancey will continue to serve as the company’s Chief Executive [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SAN FRANCISCO (April 14, 2021) &#8212; Emtrain, which delivers workplace culture analytics<br />
through its online training platform to prevent bias, discrimination, harassment and ethical<br />
lapses in the workplace, today announced it has hired Odessa (OJ) Jenkins to be the<br />
company’s first president. Emtrain’s founder Janine Yancey will continue to serve as the<br />
company’s Chief Executive Officer.</p>
<p>Prior to joining Emtrain, Jenkins served as Vice President of Client Success at YourCause, an<br />
enterprise software company that enabled corporate social responsibility, where she helped<br />
grow the team from 40 to 200 people. She also founded the Women’s National Football<br />
Conference, a professional women’s tackle football league which has teams in 20 cities.<br />
“OJ does not look or sound like your typical Silicon Valley executive. That’s a feature, not a<br />
bug,“ said Yancey. “OJ is passionate about our mission to strengthen workplace culture with<br />
stronger ethics, deeper respect and greater inclusion. She also has deep experience leading<br />
and managing an enterprise software company: a rarity for any woman and particularly for a<br />
woman of color.”</p>
<p>“I believe in the ability of companies to change the world,” Jenkins said. “I know the impact<br />
that company culture can have on employees, their productivity, their attitude, and their own<br />
well-being. I believe company culture is about authenticity. Emtrain is proof of this. I got to<br />
where I am by being my absolute authentic self. I know I don’t fit the mold for the typical<br />
president of a tech startup. For some companies that might be scary. For Emtrain, it’s<br />
exciting.”</p>
<p>As President, Jenkins’ responsibility will be to continue to drive Emtrain’s growth as a<br />
CultureTech company. In the last two years, Emtrain has doubled its employee count,<br />
launched EmtrainAI, a pioneering learning and analytics platform, and published extensive<br />
research on workplace culture based on the 25 million employee sentiment points across its<br />
Workplace Culture Benchmark<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />. Recognized as one of the 250 fastest growing companies in<br />
California by Inc. Magazine, with revenues nearly doubling between 2018 -2020, Emtrain’s<br />
customers include leading brands such as Bed Bath &amp; Beyond, Indeed, Genentech, Chevron,<br />
and Glassdoor.</p>
<p>As Emtrain’s CEO, Yancey’s focus will be on broader company thought leadership and<br />
developing deeper relationships with clients, partners and community members.</p>
<p>“OJ is an athlete and coach and is passionate about equality in women’s sports, just like she’s<br />
passionate about equality in business.” Yancey said. “Every hire is an opportunity to<br />
strengthen Emtrain’s social fabric and make our team more diverse and robust. I’m delighted<br />
to bring OJ on board as our President to help us scale and make a big social impact.”</p>
<p><strong>About Emtrain<br />
</strong>Emtrain&#8217;s workplace culture platform captures the dynamics for the three social indicators of<br />
respect, inclusion and ethics as employees take relevant, engaging compliance training<br />
courses, and provide their sentiment to deliver unique culture analytics that drive individual<br />
and organizational behavior change. Emtrain.ai allows you to benchmark your culture<br />
against our global community to identify issues before they become toxic problems that<br />
become compliance issues and destroy culture. Emtrain partners with industry experts and<br />
uses current events to teach on topics such as sexual harassment, unconscious bias, diversity,<br />
equity, inclusion and ethics. Emtrain&#8217;s innovative platform is used by more than 600<br />
companies, such as Bed Bath &amp; Beyond, Genentech, Chevron, Buzzfeed, Indeed, Degreed,<br />
Medallia, Nerdwallet and others. Recognized by Fast Company on the &#8220;World Changing Ideas<br />
2020&#8221; list, and named one of the 250 fastest-growing companies in California by Inc.<br />
Magazine, Emtrain is a woman-owned and women-led company. Please visit<br />
<a href="https://emtrain.com/">https://emtrain.com/</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cappfinity and Lindsey Pollak Launch #2020Strong Research Project on Post-pandemic Hiring</title>
		<link>./../../../../cappfinity-and-lindsey-pollak-launch-2020strong-research-project-on-post-pandemic-hiring/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../../cappfinity-and-lindsey-pollak-launch-2020strong-research-project-on-post-pandemic-hiring/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 13:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2360</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NEW YORK, May 7, 2020 /PRNewswire/ &#8212; HR tech firm, Cappfinity is working with New York Times best-selling author and workplace expert, Lindsey Pollak on a ground-breaking global research project exploring the impact of the Covid-19 pandemic on the graduating class of 2020 and the future of graduate hiring.  Based on expert opinion from talent acquisition leaders in the UK, US and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>NEW YORK, May 7, 2020 /PRNewswire/ &#8212; HR tech firm, <a href="https://www.cappfinity.com/us/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Cappfinity </a>is working with New York Times best-selling author and workplace expert, Lindsey Pollak on a ground-breaking global research project exploring the impact of the Covid-19 pandemic on the graduating class of 2020 and the future of graduate hiring. </p>



<p>Based on expert opinion from talent acquisition leaders in the UK, US and APAC region, 2020 Strong will look at how the global pandemic is causing businesses to reshape their approach to graduate hiring, including shifts in on-campus recruiting and virtual hiring and investigating the impact on social mobility and diversity.</p>



<p>Cappfinity will be sharing their findings with employers of entry-level talent and university career services professionals through a range of digital content including a webinar series.</p>



<p>The company also plans to support the Class of 2020 and other current college students to discover their strengths and explore potential future career paths by providing free a Strengths Profile including the digital Career Guide. The Guide recommends the top&nbsp;six industry sectors based on an individual&#8217;s realized strengths, and top&nbsp;two sectors based on their unrealized strengths.</p>



<p>Cappfinity CEO, Dr Alex Linley spoke about the project, &#8220;The employment landscape is constantly shifting, creating uncertainty for both employers and graduates. While the job market may not be thriving, now more than ever employers need top talent to tackle the challenges created by the pandemic. By accessing expert global insight from industry thought leaders and sharing our strengths expertise and tools, we hope to add value to both businesses and students to help them navigate their way through these unprecedented times.&#8221;</p>



<p>Author and keynote speaker,&nbsp;Lindsey Pollak, added,<br>&#8220;There can be no doubt that the global Coronavirus pandemic is creating major challenges for both students seeking entry level jobs and internships, and businesses looking to secure high calibre graduates. I&#8217;m delighted to be working Cappfinity on 2020 Strong to support the Class of 2020. I believe it will provide much-needed, timely support for both employers and students. For a student looking to stand out in a competitive job market, being able to understand and showcase their strengths will be a distinct advantage, and the insight we can provide from industry thought leaders around the globe will help businesses to evolve hiring practices and secure the talent they need to future-proof their businesses.&#8221;</p>



<p>Contact:&nbsp;Rachael Ramos, Cappfinity,&nbsp;<a href="mailto:rachael.ramos@cappfinity.com" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">rachael.ramos@cappfinity.com</a>, +44 (0)7719 986909</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../../cappfinity-and-lindsey-pollak-launch-2020strong-research-project-on-post-pandemic-hiring/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emtrain Raises $8M in Growth Capital to Accelerate Workplace Culture Health Via AI Technology, Analytics and Benchmarking</title>
		<link>./../../../../emtrain-raises-8m-in-growth-capital-to-accelerate-workplace-culture-health-via-ai-technology-analytics-and-benchmarking/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../../emtrain-raises-8m-in-growth-capital-to-accelerate-workplace-culture-health-via-ai-technology-analytics-and-benchmarking/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2334</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Data-driven CultureTech platform sees increasing demand as global pandemic creates significant new workplace culture challenges SAN FRANCISCO – May 6, 2020 – Emtrain, an online workplace culture platform that helps companies diagnose, benchmark and prevent bad workplace culture outcomes, today announced it received $8 million in growth capital funding, led by Education Growth Partners (“EGP”), [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong><em>Data-driven CultureTech platform sees increasing demand as global pandemic creates significant new workplace culture challenges</em></strong></p>



<p>SAN FRANCISCO – May 6, 2020 – <a href="http://www.emtrain.com/">Emtrain</a>, an online workplace culture platform that helps companies diagnose, benchmark and prevent bad workplace culture outcomes, today announced it received $8 million in growth capital funding, led by Education Growth Partners (“EGP”), a private equity firm dedicated to providing growth capital to proven, high potential<br>human development and workplace companies. Signature Bank, a New York-based full-service commercial bank with 31 private client offices nationwide, serves as Emtrain’s banker and provided a $2 million facility to complement the equity investment.</p>



<p>The new funding will enable Emtrain to expand its culture tech platform to provide on-demand monitoring and analysis of key indicators that are the foundation of healthy workplace culture. Not only does Emtrain’s solution meet increasing state and federal compliance training regulations, but it also diagnoses issues that are otherwise invisible to business leaders and benchmarks those issues against a global average so that internal stakeholders know where to focus their time and attention for maximum and measurable results. The diagnostic tool and data provide a win/win for employers and employees who both want to prevent these issues but lack the visibility, tools and organizational structure to do so effectively.</p>



<p>Emtrain’s recently launched Emtrain.ai solution has already collected over seven million employee sentiment responses about core culture indicators that exist in organizations such as power dynamics; in-group/out-group dynamics; unconscious biases and other indicators that correlate with a higher risk for bad culture outcomes. The company’s initial report, Emtrain’s 2020 Workplace Culture Report , published in March, shows that only 17% of employees will report sexual harassment to HR if they see or experience it. Other data is consistent in that it shows employees don’t typically report problems. The result is these problems remain invisible to HR and compliance leaders until there’s an explosive incident<br>that rocks the culture.</p>



<p>“Our changing demographics, social norms and current tough business climate require a better solution to educate employees of their rights and responsibilities and how to be a culture leader while informing employers where they need to focus their time and attention to support a healthy culture.” said Yancey. “U.S. businesses spend five billion dollars each<br>year on compliance training without getting real business value; no business intelligence, no benchmarking, no evidence of behavior modification, nothing but a completion certificate.</p>



<p>Business leaders are increasingly demanding business value from these programs and a way to solve behavioral problems before they turn into bad outcomes. Emtrain uses data, analytics, and benchmarking to show companies where they are vulnerable and how to address their hotspots in a proactive way.”</p>



<p>“Janine has a bold, unique vision on how to change the way organizations identify their risk and prevent complex culture issues from becoming damaging,” said EGP Managing Partner Peter Campbell. “Janine Yancey and her team have developed their predictive frameworks and data sets over 15 years, and have now built a breakthrough product that anticipates where the market has moved. We’re excited to add considerable capital and our expertise in learning and behavioral change to Emtrain as they change the way employers and employees interact to prevent harassment, bias, ethical lapses and other bad culture outcomes.”</p>



<p><strong>About Emtrain</strong><br>Emtrain’s workplace culture platform reinvents compliance training with provocative content that sparks dialogue and unique culture analytics that drive individual and organizational behavior change. Emtrain.ai allows you to benchmark your culture against our global community to identify issues before they become toxic problems that become compliance issues and destroy culture. Emtrain partners with industry experts and uses current events to teach on topics such as sexual harassment, unconscious bias, and ethics. Emtrain’s innovative platform is used by more than 800 companies, such as Netflix, Yelp, Dolby, LiveNation, and others. Recognized by Fast Company as an Honorable Mention in its “World Changing Ideas 2020” list, Emtrain is a woman-owned and women-led company.</p>



<p><strong>About Education Growth Partners</strong><br>Education Growth Partners (“EGP”) is a private equity firm dedicated to providing growth capital to proven, high potential learning, data and knowledge, and workplace companies that offer compelling solutions to unmet needs. The extensive operating experience and investment expertise of Education Growth Partners’ team ensures its companies receive an<br>infusion of highly strategic capital and insight that can accelerate their reach, scale and impact to create long-term value.</p>



<p><strong>About Signature Bank</strong><br>Signature Bank, member FDIC, is a New York-based full-service commercial bank with 31 private client offices throughout the New York metropolitan area and Connecticut as well as San Francisco. The Bank’s growing network of private client banking teams serves the needs of privately-owned businesses, their owners and senior managers. Its Venture Banking Group<br>serves venture capital firms and the portfolio companies in which they invest while its Fund Banking Division provides financing and banking services to the private equity industry. For more information, please visit <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://www.signatureny.com/" target="_blank">www.signatureny.com</a>.</p>



<p>Media Contact:<br>Ryan Gerding<br>press@emtrain.com<br>OR rgerding@inkincpr.com<br>M: (816) 665-1001</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../../emtrain-raises-8m-in-growth-capital-to-accelerate-workplace-culture-health-via-ai-technology-analytics-and-benchmarking/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fuse Universal Brings Next-Level L&#038;D to the USA</title>
		<link>./../../../../fuse-universal-brings-next-level-ld-to-the-usa/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../../fuse-universal-brings-next-level-ld-to-the-usa/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2299</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From London to Cape Town to Sydney, Fuse Universal has been changing the face of Learning &#038; Development. With a number of marquee US clients already signed up, Fuse is now set to open its first US office in Boston. With an origin story that began at London’s Silicon Roundabout, it was only natural that [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>From London to Cape Town to Sydney, Fuse Universal has been changing the face of Learning &#038; Development. With a number of marquee US clients already signed up, Fuse is now set to open its first US office in Boston.</strong></p>
<p>With an origin story that began at London’s Silicon Roundabout, it was only natural that Fuse’s first US office would open in Boston’s equivalent, the Seaport District. Boston has housed and nurtured some industry giants, including Facebook, Dropbox and TripAdvisor &#8211; and Fuse’s USA client list is equally impressive, including industry giants like Hilti and Merck.</p>
<p><strong>Fuse delivers business value in a changing world</strong></p>
<p>Today, firms expect a return on their investment in L&#038;D, and they’re not getting it from traditional course-centric learning strategies. Around 70% of a traditional course accounts to almost no value whatsoever – it’s clear that a different approach is needed in order for L&#038;D to keep up with the speed of business.</p>
<p>“We are excited about the speed at which L&#038;D is changing from a course-centric view to one where a wide range of tools and techniques are woven together to solve a range of different business problems,” says Fuse founder and chief storyteller Steve Dineen. “Fuse’s expansion into North America will open up huge opportunities for companies who see learning as a strategic tool that drives business value.</p>
<p>“Everybody has to fight for their share of budgets, but companies are still spending millions annually on courses that deliver no business value at all. By making measurable business results the goal, Fuse’s mobile-first, integrated learning platform is the only solution that’s delivering proven value.”</p>
<p><strong>Right move. Right place. Right now.</strong></p>
<p>Fuse’s 150+ global clients already benefit from the support of offices in London, Cape Town and Sydney – a US office was the next logical step.</p>
<p>“Establishing a physical presence in North America will help us spearhead significant growth in the region and, combined with our existing offices, it’ll mean that we can enhance the local service and support that we provide, across the world and across time zones.”</p>
<p>Steve continues: “This move will help us grow the Fuse Tribe both internationally and within North America itself. We’re looking forward to sharing our continued success with our customers.”</p>
<p><strong>About Fuse Universal</strong></p>
<p>Fuse Universal is a learning technology company which helps large and fast-growing companies build a culture of continuous learning and drive measurable improvements in business performance. Used by over 120 customers worldwide, including Spotify, Adidas, Scandic, Vodafone, and Ogilvy, The Fuse platform combines machine learning and artificial intelligence with beautifully-designed tools to enable content curation, creation, and crowdsourcing. With its mobile-first design and community features, Fuse Universal enables companies to unlock knowledge and insights from their top-performing employees in order to teach and engage their teams worldwide, while also supporting traditional learning content and courses.</p>
<p>Fuse Universal is proud of its global education charity, FuseSchool, which supports 200,000 students online. Funded by Fuse Universal’s successful commercial business, FuseSchool is transforming the secondary school education curriculum into high-quality bitesize content, free for all to access.</p>
<p>Learn more at <a href="http://www.fuseuniversal.com/">www.fuseuniversal.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../../fuse-universal-brings-next-level-ld-to-the-usa/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tiger 21 Hires New President and Chief Executive Officer to Take Member Experience to New Heights</title>
		<link>./../../../../tiger-21-hires-new-president-and-chief-executive-officer-to-take-member-experience-to-new-heights/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../../tiger-21-hires-new-president-and-chief-executive-officer-to-take-member-experience-to-new-heights/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 13:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2330</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Premier Network of High-Net-Worth Wealth Creators Lands Education and Human Development Leader to Build Out Infrastructure and Services for Members New York, NY – June 3, 2019&#160; – TIGER 21, the premier peer membership organization for successful entrepreneurs, investors, and top executives, today announced the appointment of Timothy Daniels as its President and Chief [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong><em>The Premier Network of High-Net-Worth Wealth Creators Lands Education and Human Development Leader to Build Out Infrastructure and Services for Members</em></strong></p>



<p>New York, NY – June 3, 2019&nbsp; –<a href="https://tiger21.com/"> TIGER</a><a href="https://tiger21.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> </a><a href="https://tiger21.com/">21</a>, the premier peer membership organization for successful entrepreneurs, investors, and top executives, today announced the appointment of Timothy Daniels as its President and Chief Executive Officer (CEO). Mr. Daniels will be responsible for cultivating and deepening the Member experience, developing and expanding strategic partnerships, as well as implementing and furthering an existing international expansion plan to benefit TIGER 21’s Members. He will be taking the reins from TIGER 21 Founder Michael Sonnenfeldt who spent eighteen months guiding TIGER 21 as its interim CEO. Mr. Sonnenfeldt will be returning to his traditional role of Chairman. Mr. Daniels will report to the Executive Committee of the Board.</p>



<p>TIGER 21 provides Members with a unique and confidential forum in which to focus on improving their investment acumen while exploring issues of wealth preservation, philanthropy, estate planning, and family dynamics. TIGER 21 has over 700 Members who collectively manage personal assets of more than $70 billion.</p>



<p>“I am thrilled that Tim will bring deep expertise to better deliver on our goals of providing a Member experience that is second to none as we continue to fill out our global network and explore new products and services to best serve our Members,” said Mr. Sonnenfeldt. “No one was better qualified to lead us in this next phase of our development. We&#8217;ve selected a strong leader at a time when TIGER 21 is positioned for expansion and enhancement of the robust platform that has been instituted over the last 20 years.”</p>



<p>In his new role, Mr. Daniels is responsible for strategic, operational, and financial results of the organization, and most importantly, the delivery of an unparalleled world-class Member experience. He will leverage his deep knowledge of the education industry to design and develop new products, services, and programs that enhance Member engagement, while helping to build and lead the business through a new phase of development.</p>



<p>&nbsp;“The opportunity to build on the great work that Michael and the team have done to create exceptional experiences for TIGER 21’s Members is something truly unique and will allow me to leverage my global expertise in the field of education and human development,” said Mr. Daniels.</p>



<p>Prior to joining TIGER 21, Mr. Daniels served as CEO of Laureate Education in Europe, Middle East, Africa and Asia Pacific, overseeing these regions for the leading international universities group.&nbsp; He was based in Singapore and then London and had total operational oversight of 34 institutions in 15 countries with revenue totaling nearly $1 billion. Before that, he was President of Apollo Global, a joint venture between Apollo Group and The Carlyle Group, as well as Chairman and CEO of Wall Street Institute International.</p>



<p>A CEO with both private equity-backed and public companies experience, Mr. Daniels’s strong strategic and operating background combined with leadership, technology-enabled innovation and international capabilities, will help position TIGER 21 for continued success in both new and existing markets.</p>



<p>Peter Campbell, Managing Partner of Education Growth Partners, commented: “Tim has extensive experience in successfully leading education and development companies such as TIGER 21. Throughout his career he has demonstrated the skill to run similar high-quality, high-touch businesses efficiently while maintaining an uncompromising focus on Member experience, quality, and positive Member outcomes.”&nbsp; Education Growth Partners is an investor in TIGER 21.</p>



<p>Mr. Sonnenfeldt will continue to represent TIGER 21 in the media and to explore, with Mr. Daniels, new areas for expansion and development that can better serve TIGER 21 Members. “I have been a TIGER 21 Member, first and foremost, for 20 years, and I am excited to return to my role as Chairman, which allows me to spend more time with Members,” added Mr. Sonnenfeldt.</p>



<p><br>&nbsp;Mr. Daniels graduated from the University of Wisconsin and received his Master of Business Administration from the University of Chicago.</p>



<p>&nbsp;For more information about the TIGER 21 Membership experience, please see <a href="https://tiger21.com/membership/member-experience" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">here</a>.</p>



<p><strong>About TIGER 21</strong></p>



<p>TIGER 21 is the premier peer membership organization for high-net-worth wealth creators and preservers that helps them to navigate the challenges and opportunities that success creates. TIGER 21’s 700+ Members collectively manage personal assets of $70+ billion. Members are current and former entrepreneurs, investors and top executives. TIGER 21 leads with a unique approach to financial acumen and wealth preservation that focuses on leveraging collective wisdom, shining a light on personal blind spots, and engaging Members in an extraordinary community to protect, connect, and enhance their lives. Founded in 1999, TIGER 21 is headquartered in New York City and has confidential Groups of 12-15 Members each that meet for a full day each month in Atlanta, Austin, Boston, Charlotte, Chicago, Dallas, Denver, Detroit, Houston, Los Angeles, Miami, Naples, Nashville, New York City, Newport Beach, Palm Beach, Philadelphia, San Diego, San Francisco, Scottsdale, Seattle, Tampa Bay, and Washington, DC as well as international Groups in Calgary, Edmonton, London (UK), Montreal, Toronto, Vancouver, in addition to Zurich.&nbsp; Each Group functions as a personal board of directors for its constituent Members. Membership is by invitation only. To learn more about TIGER 21, please visit <a href="http://www.tiger21.com/">www.TIGER21.com</a>.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../../tiger-21-hires-new-president-and-chief-executive-officer-to-take-member-experience-to-new-heights/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apex Learning Names Jean Sharp Its Chief Academic Officer</title>
		<link>./../../../../apex-learning-names-jean-sharp-its-chief-academic-officer/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../../apex-learning-names-jean-sharp-its-chief-academic-officer/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 13:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2290</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Apex Learning, a recognized leader in online learning for secondary education, announced that Jean Sharp has been appointed to the newly created position of Chief Academic Officer. Sharp will play a key role in ensuring the company’s curriculum solutions align with the needs of educators today and are effective in achieving outcomes, particularly with struggling [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Apex Learning</strong>, a recognized leader in online learning for secondary education, announced that Jean Sharp has been appointed to the newly created position of Chief Academic Officer. Sharp will play a key role in ensuring the company’s curriculum solutions align with the needs of educators today and are effective in achieving outcomes, particularly with struggling students and English language learners.</p>
<p>For the past seven years, Sharp has been the head of content development for Apex Learning. Prior to joining Apex Learning, Sharp served as the Vice President of Curriculum and Instruction for AdvancePath Academics where she was responsible for overseeing curriculum design and implementation in the company’s dropout recovery schools. Previously, Sharp was Vice President of Curriculum Development at PLATO Learning Inc and Executive Producer at MECC/The Learning Company. Among her credits are numerous award-winning educational software products, published for both school and consumer markets.</p>
<p>Sharp began her career as a classroom teacher in Illinois where she saw how eager students were to use technology, fueling her interest in not only how digital learning engages students, but also how it supports their academic achievement. Sharp holds a Master’s Degree in Educational Technology and Instructional Design from the University of Oklahoma.</p>
<p>“As a company that serves schools, we believe it is extremely important that the educator’s perspective is represented on our leadership team,” said Cheryl Vedoe, CEO, Apex Learning. “With her rich background in education, Jean Sharp has been an extraordinary asset to our company and will continue to have great impact as our Chief Academic Officer.”</p>
<p><strong>About Apex Learning</strong><br />
Schools and districts nationwide implement Apex Learning digital curriculum to personalize the learning experience and support success for all students&#8211;from those who are struggling to those capable of accelerating. Proven to increase outcomes, Apex Learning digital curriculum actively engages students in learning, with embedded supports and scaffolds to meet the needs of diverse learners. During the most recent school year, there were more than 3.6 million enrollments in Apex Learning digital curriculum. Headquartered in Seattle, Apex Learning is accredited by AdvancEd and its courses are approved for National Collegiate Athletic Association eligibility. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.apexlearning.com/">www.apexlearning.com</a>  contact or call 1.800.453.1454.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../../apex-learning-names-jean-sharp-its-chief-academic-officer/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MODO ACQUIRES ULYNGO BRINGING MARKETPLACE CAPABILITIES TO ITS NO-CODE CAMPUS APP SOLUTION FOR UNIVERSITIES</title>
		<link>./../../../../modo-acquires-ulyngo-bringing-marketplace-capabilities-to-its-no-code-campus-app-solution-for-universities/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../../modo-acquires-ulyngo-bringing-marketplace-capabilities-to-its-no-code-campus-app-solution-for-universities/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 13:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2314</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Modo Makes it Easy for Customers to Build and Manage a Mobile Marketplace of Storefronts Within Their Campus App Modo Labs®, the leading no-code mobile app development platform used by the world’s most recognized and respected institutions of higher education, today announced the acquisition of Ulyngo, a leader in enabling and securing student and campus [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Modo Makes it Easy for Customers to Build and Manage a Mobile Marketplace of Storefronts Within Their Campus App</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.modolabs.com/">Modo Labs</a>®, the leading no-code mobile app development platform used by the world’s most recognized and respected institutions of higher education, today announced the acquisition of <a href="https://ulyngo.com/">Ulyngo</a>, a leader in enabling and securing student and campus commerce.</p>
<p>With this acquisition, Modo will introduce a powerful commercial gateway, Modo Marketplace<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> and expand on the capabilities of the Modo Campus® solution. Modo Marketplace will facilitate safe and authenticated transactions between students, student organizations, university departments, and more, all within their campus app. With the new commerce capabilities, customers can quickly build a campus app enabling a student to buy a bike from a classmate, register for a university 5K run, pay club membership dues, or sell textbooks to their campus bookstore. Every transaction will be processed securely through the PCI-compliant Modo Marketplace payment system and can be integrated with existing university payment gateways and student ID card providers.</p>
<p>Adding Ulyngo and the Modo Marketplace is a natural evolution of the <a href="https://www.modolabs.com/products/modo-campus/">Modo Campus</a> capabilities, from publishing to communications and commerce, further empowering students to be the content creators within their campus apps.</p>
<p>“We have been searching for ways to better reach students with the services and information they need and use most, especially when it comes to commerce. Ulyngo and Modo together will allow us to do just that,” said Aaron Ochoa, Director at the University of California, Davis Stores.</p>
<p>“Our vision is to transform the campus digital experience (DX) by helping our customers engage their mobile-first students,” said Stewart Elliot, CEO of Modo. “The addition of Ulyngo to the Modo no-code app development platform is a critical component and logical next step to doing so. By adding robust e-commerce capabilities, we’re bringing the full student lifecycle to a mobile experience and beyond.”</p>
<p>“When we created Ulyngo, our mission was to establish a new way for students to safely and easily, transact and engage on campus. By joining Modo, we will have the opportunity to expand upon that mission and reach campuses across the globe,” said Alex Jekowsky, Founder and CEO of Ulyngo. “We are excited to join Modo and together create a single solution that can unify all elements of the student experience.”</p>
<p>Modo and Ulyngo already share multiple joint customers, offering a proven and market-tested integrated combination. The next-generation vision to offer e-commerce capabilities throughout the Modo product suite is already under development, driving transformation of Modo Marketplace from a point solution to an expansive PCI-compliant platform that enables every activity, event, department, and campus organization to leverage a secure marketplace using their campus app.</p>
<p><strong>About Modo</strong><br />
Trusted by hundreds of the world’s most recognized universities and brands from around the world, the Modo no-code app platform offers enterprise-scale mobile engagement and communication capabilities that allow users to quickly and easily create unified mobile campus and workplace experiences that increase connectivity for employees, students, faculty, and guests. Using Modo, customers quickly unlock innovation and digitally transform their organizations by empowering the domain expertise of any person within their organization, regardless of technical skill set. For more information, visit <a href="https://www.modolabs.com/">modolabs.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../../modo-acquires-ulyngo-bringing-marketplace-capabilities-to-its-no-code-campus-app-solution-for-universities/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kronos Incorporated Partners with Human Capital Institute to Explore Innovative Talent Acquisition Strategies</title>
		<link>./../../../../kronos-incorporated-partners-with-human-capital-institute-to-explore-innovative-talent-acquisition-strategies/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../../kronos-incorporated-partners-with-human-capital-institute-to-explore-innovative-talent-acquisition-strategies/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2302</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[New Research Reveals How High Performing Organizations Attract &#038; Hire Top Talent Differently The Human Capital Institute (HCI), the first-choice learning partner for HR professionals, announces the release of new research, “How High Performing Organizations Compete for Talent: Evolving Strategies for Attracting and Hiring a Complex Workforce.” Conducted in partnership with Kronos Incorporated, a leading [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>New Research Reveals How High Performing Organizations Attract &#038; Hire Top Talent Differently</strong></p>
<p>The Human Capital Institute (HCI), the first-choice learning partner for HR professionals, announces the release of new research, “How High Performing Organizations Compete for Talent: Evolving Strategies for Attracting and Hiring a Complex Workforce.” Conducted in partnership with Kronos Incorporated, a leading provider of human capital management solutions, the research examines how organizations are improving talent acquisition in today’s dynamic, highly competitive job market.</p>
<p>Candidates are in the driver’s seat. As new jobs open that require new and different skills, the talent acquisition process becomes more expensive and time-consuming. Complex workforces comprised of full-time, part-time, and contract or freelance workers all present unique challenges. HR and recruiting professionals are under more pressure than ever to make the right hire.</p>
<p>“High-performing organizations face the same hiring challenges as their competitors, but they’re charting a different course to overcome obstacles,” said Jenna Filipkowski, HCI’s Head of Research. “For example, they focus on hiring for learning aptitude rather than skills alone, creating a stronger pipeline of talent to meet current and future business needs.”</p>
<p>Based on an online survey of over 200 organizations, as well as thought leader interviews and secondary research, HCI and Kronos found that recruiting strategies at high performing organizations:</p>
<p>Emphasize the development of strong internal pipelines for talent as much as external pipelines<br />
Are more likely to offer comprehensive total reward packages, developmental opportunities, and flexible work arrangements<br />
Customize processes for talent segments to effectively reach different types of candidates<br />
Research findings will be discussed in depth in a complimentary webcast taking place on March 26, 2019 at 1:00pm ET. All registrants will receive a copy of the <a href="http://www.hci.org/hr-research/how-high-performing-organizations-compete-talent-evolving-strategies-attracting-and">research report</a>  .</p>
<p><strong>About Kronos Incorporated</strong><br />
Kronos is a leading provider of workforce management and human capital management cloud solutions. Kronos industry-centric workforce applications are purpose-built for businesses, healthcare providers, educational institutions, and government agencies of all sizes. Tens of thousands of organizations — including half of the Fortune 1000® — and more than 40 million people in over 100 countries use Kronos every day. Visit <a href="http://www.kronos.com/">www.kronos.com</a></p>
<p><strong>About Human Capital Institute (HCI)</strong><br />
Human Capital Institute is the first choice for HR professionals and organizations who have decided to accelerate their journey from traditional, tactical specialists to strategic, high-impact business partners. HCI seeks to educate, empower, and validate strategic talent management professionals to impact business results through the acquisition of insights, skills and tools that are contextualized through research, practice, expert guidance, peer learning, and self-discovery. Visit <a href="http://www.hci.org/">HCI.org</a> to learn more.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../../kronos-incorporated-partners-with-human-capital-institute-to-explore-innovative-talent-acquisition-strategies/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MODO LABS BOLSTERS ITS LEADERSHIP TEAM WITH THE APPOINTMENT OF CHIEF MARKETING OFFICER</title>
		<link>./../../../../modo-labs-bolsters-its-leadership-team-with-the-appointment-of-chief-marketing-officer/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../../modo-labs-bolsters-its-leadership-team-with-the-appointment-of-chief-marketing-officer/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 14:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../../index.html?p=2310</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To build on the company’s high-growth enterprise customer strategy and market leadership in higher-education, a newly created role of Chief Marketing Officer (CMO) has been added to Modo’s executive team Modo Labs, developer of the world’s leading mobile engagement platform, today announced the appointment of Rebecca Murtagh as CMO. With decades of high-tech B2B marketing [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To build on the company’s high-growth enterprise customer strategy and market leadership in higher-education, a newly created role of Chief Marketing Officer (CMO) has been added to Modo’s executive team</strong></p>
<p>Modo Labs, developer of the world’s leading mobile engagement platform, today announced the appointment of Rebecca Murtagh as CMO. With decades of high-tech B2B marketing experience, Murtagh will lead and execute Modo’s go-to-market strategy, to build on this year’s record-breaking customer growth in higher education and enterprise markets. Murtagh will report to Modo’s CEO Stewart Elliot.</p>
<p>Murtagh’s experience spans multi-billion dollar companies to high-growth start-ups. Most recently, as the lead marketing executive for branding and corporate communications at Zerto, she established the company as an IT resilience leader. Prior to Zerto, Murtagh was Vice President of Global Marketing at Akamai. Her career at Akamai spanned over 16 years, during which time she led the globalization of marketing operations and branding and spearheaded the design and execution of the company’s digital marketing strategy.</p>
<p>“Today employees and students alike expect engaging mobile experiences in every aspect of their lives,” said Murtagh. “With Modo, universities and enterprises can easily deliver just that. I’m excited to be joining the founders and leadership team and for the opportunity to build on the momentum Modo has achieved in the marketplace.</p>
<p>Murtagh added, “My mission at Modo will be to accelerate the growth of the Modo brand and to ensure that anyone leading a next generation workplace or campus transformation will already know that Modo’s platform makes it easy to build a mobile-first experience that will not only delight users but be the technology foundation for their digital campus and workplace.”</p>
<p>“We are very pleased and excited to have someone of Rebecca’s caliber join the Modo team,” said Stewart Elliot, Chief Executive Officer of Modo Labs. “Rebecca’s in-depth enterprise experience and proven marketing, branding and alliance-building skills will accelerate our expansion efforts as we scale for future growth.</p>
<p><strong>About Modo Labs</strong><br />
Trusted by hundreds of universities and companies around the world, Modo Labs offers an enterprise-scale mobile engagement and communication platform that allows customers to quickly and easily create campus or workplace apps that engage students, staff, visitors, and prospects. By using Modo, our customers quickly unlock innovation and digitally transform their organizations by harnessing the domain skills of any person in their organization, regardless of technical skill set. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.modolabs.com/">modolabs.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../../modo-labs-bolsters-its-leadership-team-with-the-appointment-of-chief-marketing-officer/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
