<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Investments &#8211; Education Growth Partners</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 18:56:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Edmentum to Acquire Apex Learning, an Industry Leader in Virtual and Hybrid Learning for Middle and High School Students</title>
		<link>./../../../edmentum-to-acquire-apex-learning-an-industry-leader-in-virtual-and-hybrid-learning-for-middle-and-high-school-students/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2430</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BLOOMINGTON, MN / ACCESSWIRE / June 22, 2021 / Edmentum (edmentum.com), a global pioneer in education technology, announced a definitive agreement to acquire Apex Learning, a Seattle-based industry leader in digital curriculum and virtual learning with over 20 years of deep expertise providing high-quality, rigorous, and teacher-centered programs. Apex&#8217;s mission of making a difference in [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p data-reader-unique-id="1"><strong data-reader-unique-id="2">BLOOMINGTON, MN / ACCESSWIRE / June 22, 2021 / </strong>Edmentum <a href="https://www.edmentum.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:(edmentum.com" data-rapid_p="7" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="3">(edmentum.com</a>), a global pioneer in education technology, announced a definitive agreement to acquire Apex Learning, a Seattle-based industry leader in digital curriculum and virtual learning with over 20 years of deep expertise providing high-quality, rigorous, and teacher-centered programs. Apex&#8217;s mission of making a difference in education complements Edmentum&#8217;s drive to amplify teaching and propel student learning forward. Together, these two organizations will support millions of students worldwide.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="4">&#8220;I am thrilled to welcome Apex into the Edmentum family,&#8221; said Jamie Candee, Edmentum CEO. &#8220;As the school year comes to an end and districts evolve into new models of teaching for the fall, so too must Edmentum continue to grow to meet those needs. Pairing Apex&#8217;s proven, high-quality secondary learning programs with Edmentum&#8217;s full suite of high-quality, online learning programs creates a rich array of offerings designed specifically for the next generation of learners. Together, in partnership with schools and districts globally, we will move education forward.&#8221;</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="5">Edmentum&#8217;s research-based approach offers hundreds of state- and nationally certified courses, supported by comprehensive consulting and educational services. Adding Apex&#8217;s credit-bearing core and elective courses, project-based technology courses, and student-targeted, standards-matching tutorials will create a new industry-leading model for virtual and hybrid learning programs.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="10">&#8220;I am incredibly proud of the positive impact that Apex&#8217;s programs and services have had with students and educators across the country,&#8221; said Chris Porter, Apex Learning CEO. &#8220;We are absolutely committed to high-quality learning content and scalable technology and are very tightly aligned to Edmentum&#8217;s strategic vision. As we come together to work with schools to help provide students flexible learning models, the possibilities are endless. I am thrilled for the next phase of Apex and our combined ability to accelerate world-class instructional solutions for all students and educators.&#8221;</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="11">Andy Kaplan, Managing General Partner at Education Growth Partners, Apex&#8217;s prior investor, said, &#8220;We look forward to seeing Apex and Edmentum further raise the bar for digital learning and better prepare students for success. We&#8217;re proud to see our belief and investment in Apex result in such an important event in the education technology market.&#8221;</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="12">The acquisition follows a strategic investment in Edmentum last year by Chicago-based private investment firm The Vistria Group that signaled new growth for Edmentum to address the learning needs of 21st-century classrooms.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="13">&#8220;This acquisition enriches Edmentum&#8217;s depth in middle and high school grades and strengthens the company&#8217;s commitment to delivering high-quality, research-based online learning to schools and districts across the globe,&#8221; said Phil Alphonse, Senior Partner at The Vistria Group. &#8220;Bringing these two organizations together will propel even more teachers and students forward and create countless opportunities for hybrid and virtual learning all over the world.&#8221;</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="14">Apex Learning customers and products will continue to be supported as Edmentum and Apex work in concert to provide the high-quality service and experience students and educators have come to expect.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="15">The international law firm of Winston &amp; Strawn LLP is acting as legal advisor to Edmentum. William Blair &amp; Company, LLC was the lead banker for Apex Learning. Alvarez &amp; Marsal and Cuesta Partners served in a consultant and advisory capacity as well. Kramer Levin Naftalis &amp; Frankel LLP is acting as legal advisor to Apex Learning.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="16"><strong data-reader-unique-id="17">About Edmentum</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="18">Edmentum, Inc., a global leader in education technology, is committed to helping educators individualize learning for every student through simple technology, high-quality content, and actionable data. Edmentum is committed to being educators&#8217; most trusted partner in creating successful student outcomes everywhere learning occurs. Built on 60 years of experience in education, Edmentum solutions like Edmentum Courseware, Exact Path, Study Island, and EdOptions Academy, currently support educators and students in more than 40,000 schools nationwide and internationally. For more information, visit <a href="http://link.email.dynect.net/link.php?DynEngagement=true&amp;H=tiMleQXvuhG3cVWUKKJFwgesMDniOk1PHbBHFzJ47RtQGrfqda%2FT%2FTRNHRe4oo%2BfkGgl6U5DPuq1YvywU6MvFqddoLvsptF3R5kMEbc9tGCYMJRyyRysVQ%3D%3D&amp;G=0&amp;R=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.edmentum.com%2F&amp;I=20161003125215.000001a9636c%40mail6-08-ewr&amp;X=MHwxMDQ2NzU4OjU3ZjI1NDc5MGU4NWI4NDA2M2RkNDQ1Mzs%3D&amp;S=jnFIz8VOBGb6WB_y-QYkJ_W8hfpyHR51G9ziJZh7fEw" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:edmentum.com" data-rapid_p="9" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="19">edmentum.com</a>.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="20"><strong data-reader-unique-id="21">About Apex Learning</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="22">An industry leader in digital learning with deep expertise in online learning, Apex Learning collaborates with school districts across the country to implement solutions proven to accelerate learning and create opportunities for student success in school and beyond. The company is driven by the understanding that supporting the needs of all students &#8211; from struggling to advanced &#8211; strengthens schools and creates stronger communities, brighter futures, and a more equitable world. Apex Learning is accredited by Cognia and its courses are approved for National Collegiate Athletic Association eligibility. Apex Learning, where opportunity thrives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.apexlearning.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:http://www.apexlearning.com/" data-rapid_p="10" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="23">http://www.apexlearning.com/</a>.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="24"><strong data-reader-unique-id="25">About Education Growth Partners</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="26">Education Growth Partners (&#8220;EGP&#8221;) is a private equity firm dedicated to investing in proven, high potential learning, knowledge, and workplace companies that offer compelling solutions to unmet needs. The extensive investment expertise of Education Growth Partners&#8217; team ensures its companies receive an infusion of highly strategic capital and insight that can accelerate their reach, scale, and impact to create long-term value. Our highly experienced team is composed of investors with operating experience who have a passion for education and behavior change and an understanding of the power of great companies to create opportunities for individuals, organizations, and systems. For more information, please visit <a href="http://www.edgrowth.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:www.edgrowth.com" data-rapid_p="11" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="27">www.edgrowth.com</a>.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="28"><strong data-reader-unique-id="29">About</strong><strong data-reader-unique-id="30">The Vistria Group</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="31">The Vistria Group is a Chicago-based private investment firm focused on investing in middle-market companies in the healthcare, education, and financial services sectors. Vistria&#8217;s team is comprised of highly experienced operating partners and private equity executives with proven track records of working with management teams in building innovative, market-leading companies. For more information, please visit <a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;l=en&amp;o=2684714-1&amp;h=1474294993&amp;u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vistria.com%2F&amp;a=www.vistria.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:www.vistria.com" data-rapid_p="12" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="32">www.vistria.com</a>.</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="33"><strong data-reader-unique-id="34">Media Contacts</strong></p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="35"><strong data-reader-unique-id="36">Edmentum:</strong><br data-reader-unique-id="37" />Ashlee Tatum-Eckley<br data-reader-unique-id="38" /><a href="mailto:ashlee.tatum-eckley@edmentum.com" data-ylk="slk:ashlee.tatum-eckley@edmentum.com" data-rapid_p="13" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="39">ashlee.tatum-eckley@edmentum.com</a><br data-reader-unique-id="40" />214.294.9904</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="41"><strong data-reader-unique-id="42">The Vistria Group:</strong><br data-reader-unique-id="43" />Kevin Sajdak<br data-reader-unique-id="44" />Res Publica Group<br data-reader-unique-id="45" /><a href="mailto:ks@respublicagroup.com" data-ylk="slk:ks@respublicagroup.com" data-rapid_p="14" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="46">ks@respublicagroup.com</a><br data-reader-unique-id="47" />312.755.3547</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="48"><strong data-reader-unique-id="49">SOURCE:</strong> Edmentum</p>
<p data-reader-unique-id="50"><br data-reader-unique-id="52" />View source version on accesswire.com: <br data-reader-unique-id="53" /><a href="https://www.accesswire.com/652677/Edmentum-to-Acquire-Apex-Learning-an-Industry-Leader-in-Virtual-and-Hybrid-Learning-for-Middle-and-High-School-Students" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-ylk="slk:https://www.accesswire.com/652677/Edmentum-to-Acquire-Apex-Learning-an-Industry-Leader-in-Virtual-and-Hybrid-Learning-for-Middle-and-High-School-Students" data-rapid_p="15" data-v9y="1" data-reader-unique-id="54">https://www.accesswire.com/652677/Edmentum-to-Acquire-Apex-Learning-an-Industry-Leader-in-Virtual-and-Hybrid-Learning-for-Middle-and-High-School-Students</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emtrain</title>
		<link>./../../../emtrain/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../emtrain/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 19:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Emtrain is a data-driven online training platform with modern content, interactive learning scenarios, and video-based microlessons.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="http://www.emtrain.com/"><strong>Emtrain&#8217;s</strong></a> workplace culture platform reinvents compliance training with provocative content that sparks dialogue and unique culture analytics that drive individual and organizational behavior change. Emtrain.ai allows you to benchmark your culture against our global community to identify issues before they become toxic problems that become compliance issues and destroy culture. Emtrain, founded and run by Janine Yancey, partners with industry experts and uses current events to teach on topics such as sexual harassment, unconscious bias, and ethics. Emtrain’s innovative platform is used by more than 800 culture-focused companies.</p>
<p><em><a href="http://www.emtrain.com/"><strong>www.emtrain.com</strong></a></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../emtrain/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tiger 21</title>
		<link>./../../../tiger-21/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../tiger-21/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 17:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[World’s leading peer-to-peer learning network for High Net Worth individuals.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.tiger21.com/">Tiger 21</a> is a membership organization where HNW individuals who meet certain wealth criteria can apply to join a&nbsp;member group. Each group is geographically concentrated&nbsp;and consists of 8-15 HNW individuals who meet once per&nbsp;month for a full day that is curated and guided by a Tiger 21 chairperson to: a) discuss investment climate and&nbsp;opportunities, b) trade ideas and actual deals, and c) discuss, in an open forum, the particular personal and family&nbsp;challenges that arise from having and managing significant&nbsp;wealth, including wealth preservation, philanthropy, estate&nbsp;planning, and, crucially, family and other relationship dynamics.</p>
<p><em><a href="http://www.tiger21.com/"><strong>www.tiger21.com</strong></a></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../tiger-21/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All Campus</title>
		<link>./../../../all-campus/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../all-campus/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 13:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2274</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[All Campus is an Online Program Manager that partners with non-profit, traditional institutions of higher education to provide essential support, helping clients explore the possibilities of online learning.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.allcampus.com/"><strong>All Campus</strong></a> offers comprehensive, customized Online Program Manager (OPM) services to its university partners including marketing, curriculum development, enrollment, recruitment and retention — all with their partner’s unique identity and brand top of mind. All Campus provides higher educational institutions with an alternative to the traditional OPM model, which typically requires universities to outsource curriculum development and relinquish control of enrollment and other decisions. All Campus&#8217; expertise and upfront marketing investment enables their partners to connect their academic program with qualified students, increase enrollment and maximize market share.</p>
<p><em><a href="http://www.allcampus.com/"><strong>www.allcampus.com</strong></a></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../all-campus/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capp</title>
		<link>./../../../capp/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../capp/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 21:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2233</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Authentic assessment solutions for recruiting using their unique Strengths methodology, delivering better outcomes for diversity, performance and retention, all wrapped in engaging and immersive candidate experiences.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://capp.co/"><strong>Capp</strong></a> provides authentic assessment solutions for business talent using their unique Strengths methodology, delivering better outcomes for diversity, performance and retention, all wrapped in engaging and immersive candidate experiences. Capp delivers 1m+ assessments per year, completed by candidates in over 57 countries around the globe. For over ten years, Capp has been recognized as a world leader in strengths-based assessment, underpinning its new assessment innovation in immersive job simulation, live experiences, and virtual reality.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong><em><a href="http://www.capp.co/">www.capp.co</a></em></strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../capp/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Apex Learning</title>
		<link>./../../../apex-learning/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../apex-learning/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 13:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Digital curriculum designed to actively engage students in learning—combining embedded supports and scaffolds to meet diverse student needs, actionable data to inform instruction, and success management—with proven results.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://apexlearning.com/"><strong>Apex Learning</strong></a> puts rigorous, standard-based curriculum within reach for all students—from those struggling to those capable of acceleration—to prepare them for the next course, the next stage in their education, work and life. Schools and districts nationwide implement Apex Learning digital curriculum to personalize the learning experience and support success for all students—from those who are struggling to those capable of accelerating. Proven to increase outcomes, Apex Learning digital curriculum actively engages students in learning, with embedded supports and scaffolds to meet the needs of diverse learners. During the most recent school year, there have been over three million enrollments in Apex Learning Comprehensive Courses and Adaptive Tutorials. Headquartered in Seattle, Apex Learning is accredited by AdvancEd and its courses are approved for National Collegiate Athletic Association eligibility. </p>
<p class="p1"><strong><em><a href="http://www.apexlearning.com/">www.apexlearning.com</a></em></strong></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../apex-learning/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Modo Labs</title>
		<link>./../../../modo-labs/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../modo-labs/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 22:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2108</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The leading mobile engagement platform for universities and corporations that empowers both technical and non-technical staff to quickly create campus and enterprise apps.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Modo Labs</strong>&#8216; mobile solution empowers ordinary people to create extraordinary campus apps that enhance student and employee engagement and retention.  A unique combination of powerful data access, ease-of-use, and communication capabilities ensures an exceptional mobile experience, achievable by any non-technical person with minimal investment and resources. More than 125 universities, corporations and hospitals use Modo&#8217;s solution to deliver feature-rich native apps as an integral part of their digital strategy.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong><em><a href="http://www.modolabs.com/">www.modolabs.com</a></em></strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../modo-labs/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gordian Group</title>
		<link>./../../../the-gordian-group/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../the-gordian-group/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 07:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1712</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A leading provider of innovative construction data, software and services to organizations pursuing efficient and effective construction planning, estimating and procurement.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://thegordiangroup.com/home.aspx"><strong>The Gordian Group</strong></a> is the leading provider of innovative construction data, software and services to organizations pursuing efficient and effective construction planning, estimating and procurement. As the pioneer of Job Order Contracting, Gordian’s ever-growing portfolio of procurement solutions leverages highly specialized cloud-based project management software to deliver rapid deployment and long-term cost savings for the nation’s facility and infrastructure owners. Today, The Gordian Group draws on its highly specialized engineers, software and unique proprietary data sets to solve the construction information, planning and management needs of people in building construction, building products manufacturing, education, healthcare, retail, insurance, legal, and government.</p>
<p><em><strong><a href="http://thegordiangroup.com/home.aspx">www.thegordiangroup.com</a></strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../the-gordian-group/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Human Capital Institute</title>
		<link>./../../../human-capital-institute/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../human-capital-institute/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 06:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1689</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Global association for strategic talent management with over 195,000 global members who participate in HCI communities, research, education and events.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><a href="http://www.hci.org/"><strong>HCI</strong></a> is the global association for strategic talent management and new economy leadership, and a clearinghouse for best practices and new ideas. Our network of expert practitioners, Fortune 1000 and Global 2000 corporations, government agencies, global consultants and business schools contribute a stream of constantly evolving information, the best of which is organized, analyzed and shared with members through HCI communities, research, education and events.</p>
<p><em><strong><a href="http://www.hci.org/">www.hci.org</a></strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../human-capital-institute/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>eScholar</title>
		<link>./../../../escholar/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../escholar/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 06:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investments]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1687</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Developer of educational data management and educational data warehousing solutions.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1"><a href="http://www.escholar.com/"><strong>eScholar</strong></a> is the leader in education data solutions. eScholar’s award-winning solutions have an impact on over 20 million students in 5,000 school districts across 13 states. Since 1997, eScholar solutions have set the standard education data integration and quality management.</p>
<p><em><strong><a href="http://www.escholar.com/">www.escholar.com</a></strong></em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../escholar/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
