<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Education Growth Partners</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 16:50:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>MODO LABS BOLSTERS ITS LEADERSHIP TEAM WITH THE APPOINTMENT OF CHIEF MARKETING OFFICER</title>
		<link>./../../../modo-labs-bolsters-its-leadership-team-with-the-appointment-of-chief-marketing-officer/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../modo-labs-bolsters-its-leadership-team-with-the-appointment-of-chief-marketing-officer/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 14:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2310</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To build on the company’s high-growth enterprise customer strategy and market leadership in higher-education, a newly created role of Chief Marketing Officer (CMO) has been added to Modo’s executive team Modo Labs, developer of the world’s leading mobile engagement platform, today announced the appointment of Rebecca Murtagh as CMO. With decades of high-tech B2B marketing [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>To build on the company’s high-growth enterprise customer strategy and market leadership in higher-education, a newly created role of Chief Marketing Officer (CMO) has been added to Modo’s executive team</strong></p>
<p>Modo Labs, developer of the world’s leading mobile engagement platform, today announced the appointment of Rebecca Murtagh as CMO. With decades of high-tech B2B marketing experience, Murtagh will lead and execute Modo’s go-to-market strategy, to build on this year’s record-breaking customer growth in higher education and enterprise markets. Murtagh will report to Modo’s CEO Stewart Elliot.</p>
<p>Murtagh’s experience spans multi-billion dollar companies to high-growth start-ups. Most recently, as the lead marketing executive for branding and corporate communications at Zerto, she established the company as an IT resilience leader. Prior to Zerto, Murtagh was Vice President of Global Marketing at Akamai. Her career at Akamai spanned over 16 years, during which time she led the globalization of marketing operations and branding and spearheaded the design and execution of the company’s digital marketing strategy.</p>
<p>“Today employees and students alike expect engaging mobile experiences in every aspect of their lives,” said Murtagh. “With Modo, universities and enterprises can easily deliver just that. I’m excited to be joining the founders and leadership team and for the opportunity to build on the momentum Modo has achieved in the marketplace.</p>
<p>Murtagh added, “My mission at Modo will be to accelerate the growth of the Modo brand and to ensure that anyone leading a next generation workplace or campus transformation will already know that Modo’s platform makes it easy to build a mobile-first experience that will not only delight users but be the technology foundation for their digital campus and workplace.”</p>
<p>“We are very pleased and excited to have someone of Rebecca’s caliber join the Modo team,” said Stewart Elliot, Chief Executive Officer of Modo Labs. “Rebecca’s in-depth enterprise experience and proven marketing, branding and alliance-building skills will accelerate our expansion efforts as we scale for future growth.</p>
<p><strong>About Modo Labs</strong><br />
Trusted by hundreds of universities and companies around the world, Modo Labs offers an enterprise-scale mobile engagement and communication platform that allows customers to quickly and easily create campus or workplace apps that engage students, staff, visitors, and prospects. By using Modo, our customers quickly unlock innovation and digitally transform their organizations by harnessing the domain skills of any person in their organization, regardless of technical skill set. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.modolabs.com/">modolabs.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../modo-labs-bolsters-its-leadership-team-with-the-appointment-of-chief-marketing-officer/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CAPP ACQUIRES KORU&#8217;S PREDICTIVE HIRING BUSINESS</title>
		<link>./../../../capp-acquires-korus-predictive-hiring-business/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../capp-acquires-korus-predictive-hiring-business/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[egp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 14:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=2295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Acquisition provides unmatched ability to identify best fit talent, based on research about new signals for workplace success. Capp &#038; Co. Limited, a global leader in strength-based talent assessment, announces today that it has completed its acquisition of Seattle-based Koru Careers, Inc’s predictive hiring business. With the addition of Koru’s assessment of the Koru7™ Impact [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Acquisition provides unmatched ability to identify best fit talent, based on research about new signals for workplace success.</p>
<p><strong>Capp &#038; Co. Limited, a global leader in strength-based talent assessment, announces today that it has completed its acquisition of Seattle-based Koru Careers, Inc’s predictive hiring business. </strong></p>
<p>With the addition of Koru’s assessment of the Koru7<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Impact Skills and its predictive hiring platform, Capp is now able to provide enterprise employers with the ability to assess a wider range of work-related strengths and predict the fit of job applicants using machine learning and AI technologies. With this acquisition, Capp further establishes its US presence and opens its New York City head office at 450 Lexington Avenue in January 2019.</p>
<p>“We help employers to create a better aligned, motivated and &#8211; most importantly &#8211; more productive workforce,” said Dr. Alex Linley, CEO and co-founder of Capp &#038; Co. “Koru’s predictive hiring technology and deep expertise in soft skills will enable us to assess a new set of performance strengths such as grit, rigor and curiosity, and provide further insights for our customers with best of breed predictive analytics.”</p>
<p>Capp’s products and services help employers to attract, select and develop talent using in-house proprietary algorithms and validation data.</p>
<p>“Our vision has always been to level the playing field for job seekers by providing access to opportunity based on a person’s capabilities, while helping employers hire the best-fit talent,” said Kristen Hamilton, CEO and co-founder of Koru. “As part of Capp, Koru’s assessment and analytics products will be supported and enhanced by their incredibly talented team and will have broader global reach.”</p>
<p>The Koru product will continue to be offered to current and new customers and will be rebranded to Capp over the next year. Capp’s US headquarters will be in New York and Koru will be supported by a distributed team in Seattle and New York; Sydney, Australia; and London and Birmingham, UK.</p>
<p><strong>About Koru </strong></p>
<p>Headquartered in Seattle, Koru is the leader in predictive hiring based on what really drives performance. Based on the Koru7<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Impact Skills (Grit, Rigor, Impact, Teamwork, Curiosity, Ownership and Presence), Koru identifies the predictors of performance and develops models to assess fit of applicants in jobs. Koru is mobilizing the “Grit over Grades” revolution with some of the world’s leading enterprises. Koru was founded by veteran entrepreneur Kristen Hamilton, co-founder at Onvia and COO of World Learning, and Josh Jarrett, formerly of the Bill &#038; Melinda Gates Foundation and McKinsey &#038; Company.</p>
<p><strong>For further information please contact</strong> <a href="mailto:press@capp.co">press@capp.co</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../capp-acquires-korus-predictive-hiring-business/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
